[Applause]
[Music]
my my baby it is my flashing lights up
my body feels like 90s Paparazzi I'm
like my all my baby it is my kind of
night strangers daning all around me
it's like ster not the movie
fing lights upon my feels like 90s
Paparazzi but your glamorous modern
fabulous Point your cameras on oh giving
in TV Bell GG sipping on
c big energy eny just look at me look at
me look at me
go
W like my oh my baby it is my fashion
lights up my mind feels like 90s papy
I'm like my oh my baby is my Chang
daning all around me it's like straing
up a movie
[Music]
around the table like it's Vegas I'm
like Charlie with these angels taking
pictures feeling
famous I feel so Kim and CH ain't no
photosh but go be walking like a young
[Music]
Naomi when I want it it's a l
dream the me one more
time I'm like my baby this my night
flashing lights up on my b feels like 90
papazzi I'm like my oh my baby is my
kind of night changes all around me
feels like straight out of the
[Music]
movie lights up on my feels like 0